(Amy:)There was water everywhere.
(Amy:)It was such a mess.
(Leonard:)That stinks. How long are you
out of the apartment?
(Amy:)About five weeks.
Ugh! Did you lose
anything valuable?
(Amy:)Well, the pipe was
over my closet,
(Amy:)so all my
clothes are gone.
(Penny:)Oh, so nothing. Great.
(Penny:)Do they know why
the pipe burst?
(Amy:)They didn't say.
(Leonard:)Buildings
that have a combination
(Leonard:)of copper and galvanized steel
(Leonard:)are susceptible to
pinholes and corrosion
(Leonard:)caused by the mobility
of ions in the water.
(Leonard:)Can't have your head shoved
in a toilet as much as I did
(Leonard:)and not pick up a few things
about plumbing.
(Penny:)Well, if you need a place to
crash, you can stay with us.
- Really?
- Of course.
(Penny:)You can stay in Leonard's room,
and we'll stay at my place.
(Amy:)You're sure
that's not an inconvenience?
(Penny:)No, not at all.
(Leonard:)And we live with Sheldon,
so the word "inconvenience"
has really lost all meaning.
(Amy:)So, technically, I'd be
moving in with my boyfriend?
(Penny:)I guess so.
(Penny:)I'd finally get to live
alone with my husband.
(Amy:)Oh, my, this is
a big step.
(Leonard:)Mm-hmm.
(Leonard:)For two of us, it's in
the right direction.
(Sheldon:)Why are you all smiling
like crazy people?
♪ Our whole universe
was in a hot, dense state ♪